ait-pro.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy - AITpro Website Design | AITpro Website Security & Design

**AITpro Website Design**  
---  
**81 N Katherine Dr**  
**Ventura, CA   93003**  
**805-651-8516**  
  
We can be reached via email at [info@ait-pro.com](mailto:info@ait-pro.com) or by using the AITpro Contact Form or you can reach us by telephone at 805-651-8516.

For each direct visitor to our website, our web host server automatically recognizes only the visitor’s domain name, but not the email address (where possible).  For each website visitor who visits the AITpro website via a BPS Pro Affiliate Program link, the visitors IP address and Cookie is stored for 30 days in order to track cookies for the sole purpose of tracking affiliate referral sales (see Section “With respect to cookies”).  Domain names for a visitor are only used to track the amount of visitor traffic to the AITpro website (e.g. Google Analytics visitor traffic).  The email addresses of those who communicate with us via email will ONLY be used to communicate with persons requesting to be contacted. AITpro DOES NOT send unsolicited SPAM email under any circumstances.  Any correspondence, transactions and communications between AITpro clients and customers is regarded as private information and is not shared with any 3rd parties.

**With respect to cookies:**  The BPS Pro Affiliate Program does track cookies solely for the purpose of tracking affiliate referral sales.  If a website visitor has clicked on a BPS Pro Affiliate Program link from another website then the visitor’s cookie is tracked for a period of 30 days and then deleted.  This information is used for internal tracking purposes only in order to pay affiliate commission fees based on referral sales.  AITpro does not share cookie tracking information or any other information about website visitors to the AITpro website with any 3rd parties.

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an email at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number or writing to us at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding quote requests or orders they have placed on-line or regarding information they have requested. We will only contact persons requesting to be contacted.  If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us an email at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number or writing to us at the above address.

**With respect to Ad Servers:**   AITpro is not currently partnered with and does not have any special relationships with 3rd party ad server companies.

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact all persons who this may effect before we use any personal information for any reason not stated in this Privacy Policy.

Upon request we provide site visitors, clients and customers with access to all information, if any, that we maintain about them. Visitors, clients and customers can request this information by emailing us at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number or writing to us at the above address.

Any information that we have stored regarding visitors, clients and customers to the AITpro website will not be used for any other purposes other than what has been stated in the AITpro Privacy Policy.

**With respect to security:**   All sensitive personal information such as financial information is handled and processed by a PayPal SSL secure server.  AITpro does not display, expose or share your public, personal or private information with anyone unless court ordered or required by legal process.  All personal and private data is encrypted and cannot be accessed publicly.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated Privacy Policy you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number or contact your state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau or your state or local consumer protection office.
